[light music]
[Riri] And so, the friendly, handsome,
and athletic Junta Hayami…
[Junta] Uh, thanks for letting me stay.
[Riri] …has now joined
Anzu's cozy coed living arrangement.
[chuckles awkwardly]
If you want to freshen up,
the bathroom is at the end of the hall.
[Riri] This is a dream come true scenario.
One more thing.
Since this room only has two beds,
would you guys mind--
[Tsukasa and Junta] No way.
Silly me.
[Riri] It's just a matter of time
before the sparks of love fly!
Well, in that case, we can move Kazuki
into my dad's office instead.
Yeah, works for me.
It'll be great to have a room with a desk.
[meows]
DAD'S SELECTION
[dad] Yay!
-[Riri] Welcome to the love castle!
-[all groan]
-Um…
-Huh?
[Junta] She's so pretty,
I can't even look her in the eyes.
I'm late for practice.
But just let me know
if I can help out with anything, okay?
[soft chuckle]
We've got things handled here.
Right.
[sighs]
Why is all of this happening to me?
-Yeah, it's all too exciting…
-[Anzu] Get back here!
You're gonna pay
for that underwear incident!
[Riri] Give it up!
[grunts]
-[Riri screaming]
-[loud thud]
[Anzu breathes heavily]
[Anzu] I can't believe how nonchalant
Mom is being about this whole thing.
Tried to steal my underwear?
Well, I guess your old mom still got it.
MOM'S SLIGHTLY-OFF REACTION
[chuckles mischievously]
Meanwhile, there's good news.
[Anzu] I got a part-time job
at the convenience store.
Hi, welcome.
[Anzu] Kazuki's always at work,
Junta's busy with baseball,
I bet we'll barely see each other.
[theme music]
#6 A "REINCARNATED-
IN-ANOTHER-WORLD" DATE
[Junta] Morning.
-[Tsukasa] Hey.
-[Anzu yawns] Morning.
Anzu, did you get up early
to make us lunch?
Yup.
Our housemother made me.
Who are you calling "housemother"?
It's fine. Now there
are three lunches for us to make,
so I should help out too.
[groans, snores]
You offered to help.
And lettuce is not a pillow.
Hey, do you mind if I watch?
[Anzu] Watch?
I'll get nervous and mess up.
[Tsukasa] Yeah, but it won't be his fault.
You have no faith in me at all!
Fine, I'll show you. First, the pasta.
You know you're boiling chopsticks, right?
[yelps]
-[Tsukasa] You're burning Mr. Octopus.
-[Anzu screams]
[Tsukasa] And don't crack
the eggs on your forehead.
-[Anzu yelps]
-[Tsukasa] You're hopeless.
[indistinct chatter]
Hm.
Eh? What's the deal
with your lunch today? It's a mess!
-I'm usually jealous.
-[gasps]
Hmm. I know what's happening here.
You had your old bestie make it for you!
What, I-- No, it's not like that!
My little brother made it!
You're stuttering! We know you're lying!
Come on, this is so not fair.
You get a girl who's cute
and she can cook.
From the look of it, she can't cook.
I told you my little brother made it!
-Did she make him a lunch?
-Yeah.
Wow, do you think they're dating?
[sighs, chuckles]
[camera clicks]
Lies! If your little brother
did make it for you,
why are you taking a picture
and smiling like that?
-You sure look guilty.
-Hey, knock it off already!
STEWS
SKEWERED KATSU
[Tsukasa] Heading home.
Kazuki, please,
work the front of the house?
The customers love you.
What do you say, hmm?
-No thanks, I'll pass.
-That's too bad.
Kazuki, hey, wait up.
Smart turning down the front-of-house gig.
Not like you need any more fans, right?
Hey, wanna hang out? There's a new café.
We can grab a quick bite to eat
and maybe-- Uh?
Goodnight.
Okay, maybe next time.
[Tsukasa clears throat]
[exhales deeply]
[Anzu] You're home! What took so long?
[Anzu] We've been waiting for you
to start the show!
Well, hey, whoa, what show?
You forgot, huh?
The show Saki recommended. Come on.
Hurry up, go take your bath.
Well, don't take too long.
I'm falling asleep.
You really don't have to wait.
-It's more fun to watch together!
-Uh…
-Jinx.
Mm. Uh…
[Junta] We said it at the same time.
[chuckles]
[water sloshing]
[birds chirping]
[door opens]
-[Junta] I'm off to practice.
-[Tsukasa] Okay.
[Anzu] Good luck today.
You free later?
Huh?
[Tsukasa] I'll take that as a yes.
I have to go shopping today.
Would you like to come with me?
[Anzu] Me? Yeah, I guess I can.
Why not ask Makoto?
-[Tsukasa] I did. He's busy.
-[Anzu] Okay.
I guess I could.
But don't you normally shop alone?
It's nice to have a shield
from other girls.
Oh well, then I salute your hotness.
[Anzu] Seriously, though,
I buy all my clothes online,
so I don't really know
where to go around here.
[Tsukasa] It's all right,
I know where to go.
[Anzu] Can't you just shop online?
It's way easier.
I prefer in person.
Hmm.
[Anzu] Okay, let me go change.
Be right back.
-Let's go!
-[Tsukasa] Already?
LAME
[comical music]
You didn't even change your shirt.
Why change? This is a clean shirt.
We're not going grocery shopping.
The jeans are one thing, but that shirt…
How's this one?
[Tsukasa] Do you really not see it?
How about this?
[Tsukasa] All of your shirts
have cats on them?
Let me decide.
[screeches]
No, wait!
Ah! I'm drying my underwear!
[sighs]
Even your underwear looks
like something a child would wear.
-[meows]
-How dare you? These are adorable!
Please get those out of my face.
This is getting weird.
So, look.
I assumed
that you have a variety of clothing…
MEOW
[Tsukasa] …but this is all you've got!
What? And just
what is so wrong with these?
[sighs] Do you have cash?
Well, I've got
some holiday money left over.
Planning on using it?
No definitive plans, but,
I was gonna buy games with it.
[gasps]
Let's buy you new clothes.
Huh?
[screams]
It's fine to dress comfy at home,
but get normal outfits to wear in public.
Cats are normal!
[Tsukasa] Wait, I just realized,
you're gonna have to go out
shopping in these.
[Tsukasa groans]
[Riri] Sorry to interrupt,
couldn't help overhearing
and I think I can help out!
[screams]
You're still alive?
-Huh?
-Leave it to me.
I'll go help Anzu pick out
something super cute!
Just hang tight
and we'll be down in a jiff.
[chuckles]
Now that my wand is all clean again,
I can finally get back to using my magic.
Wait, the underwear thief
was totally your doing, wasn't it?
Yup! Had to cash in a favor
at headquarters for that one.
[in deep voice]
Headquarters just made my list.
Now, now, give us a smile,
you've got a big date.
So, let's go get you dressed.
We're going shopping, it's not a date.
And I'm not going
if you're gonna be weird.
Hey, stop being so mean
or I'm gonna throw everything away.
Huh?
[Riri] All of this.
Each and every outfit.
[ominous music]
-[Riri] We are ready!
-[Tsukasa] Huh?
-[door opens]
-[Riri] The wait is over.
-Here she is.
-[Anzu yelps]
Ooh.
[Anzu] Did I really have
to put on all this makeup?
This is so embarrassing.
[bright music]
Uh…
Sorry… to keep you waiting.
It's fine.
[Anzu]  Is it really hot in here,
or am I nervous?
This is really exciting.
-[Tsukasa] Let's go.
-Right.
All dressed up like that. You look nice.
[muffled grunt]
What's with your face?
[in deep voice]
I feel like I look weird in this.
Your face is weird.
[Anzu] Oh, man.
Here I am, all dressed up.
-[Anzu] Hairdo and makeup…
-Anzu!
New outfit counts as an expense.
[Anzu] On my way
to go shopping with a hot guy.
I am absolutely 100 percent
going on a date right now.
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chatter]
[Anzu in deep voice] What am I
doing here? I usually just go online
and get all the cute cat clothes
I can find.
Everyone here is so stylish.
It's like another world.
That face again?
-This is how my face looks.
-It's ugly.
[Anzu in normal voice]
Okay, that hurts.
This place is packed.
Let's do this quickly.
[Anzu] Kazuki, do you like hats?
I mean, 'cause you were wearing one
when we first met
at the convenience store too.
No, not really.
But it helps to hide my face.
-Yeah, but…
-[girls murmuring]
It doesn't seem to be working.
[groans]
So, why not wear a mask?
[Tsukasa] I tried.
Someone followed me home
thinking I was a celebrity.
[Anzu] Well, I guess there's no hiding it
when you're that good-looking.
[Anzu] Jeez,
he really hates being popular.
I wonder if that's why he moved away,
to go to a different high school?
[gasps, shivers]
-[yells] Let the games begin!
-Huh?
-[Anzu yells excitedly]
-Oh.
Uh…
[light music]
[Anzu] Whoa! Kitty pajamas!
It's cute! I want it!
[Anzu] I can't believe it.
I bought something with no cat on it?
No cat.
-Is that a big deal?
-Huh?
That's your first expense.
[Anzu] This is not good.
I let them dress me up
and I'm paying for a cute outfit
that Kazuki chose for me.
Yay!
[Anzu] It's like I'm falling
into their trap!
I'll show them. I'll only wear it
for special occasions!
[moaning]
[Anzu] I could never let Junta
see me in this.
Hungry? Do you wanna grab a bite to eat?
Sure, but…
I have to go pee before that.
Don't say "go pee."
The bathroom was over there.
Be right back, okay?
Sure, I'll find a place to eat.
Uh.
Oh, your bags.
[chuckles]
Hmm.
-Hey, look at him!
-[sighs]
[girl 1] Oh my, I wonder
if he's meeting up with someone.
-[girl 2] Such a hottie.
-[girl 3] He's so handsome. Oh, my gosh.
[sinister music]
[breathing nervously]
[Tsukasa] What's taking so long?
[sighs]
Wanna talk to him?
Think he's got a girlfriend?
Only one way to find out.
[heart thumping]
[Tsukasa] Oh, why do I have to wait
out in the open like this?
Come on, hurry up and get back.
Please, just leave me alone.
-[heart thumping]
-[static]
[female voice] Tsukasa…
-[gasping]
-[heart thumping]
[Tsukasa] Don't look at me.
[female voice echoing]
Tsukasa…
[gasps]
[Tsukasa] Go away.
Go away!
[Anzu] Kazuki!
[Tsukasa gasps]
Huh.
Sorry you had to wait,
but I found the best store ever.
Oh.
[Anzu] Quick, come look!
Huh?
[grunts]
[gentle music]
[Anzu giggling]
How did I live my life before this?
Thanks for inviting me along.
[Tsukasa] Uh…
[Anzu chuckles]
It's been fun.
Huh?
[yelps]
[Anzu] It looks just like MomohikI!
I want it, uh, but I spent all my money.
I'll come back on payday.
-I can buy it for you.
-[gasps]
[Tsukasa] As a thanks for coming with me.
Uh… Uh…
MY GOD
-[clerk] Thank you so much!
-[Anzu] Thank you so much!
[Anzu gasping]
It's so cute!
I love it so much.
I promise to take great care of it.
Okay.
Damn, it's later than I thought it was.
-[tires screeching]
-[both] Huh?
Anzu?
-Wow, you change your look.
-[soft chuckle]
It's all Riri.
It must be new. And there are no cats.
[Junta] She looks so cute.
How long have you been wearing cats
on all your clothes?
-Uh, did you two go somewhere?
-Yeah, picked up some new clothes.
No!
[Junta] Not fair, not fair…
-[Tsukasa] Stop looking at me like that.
-Not fair, not fair, not fair, not fair…
That was a long practice.
Bet you're starving.
Does teriyaki sound good?
Heck, yeah! Sounds great.
I'll start making dinner
as soon as we get home.
Can't wait.
[Anzu chuckles]
[Anzu] I was worried
Riri would spend the whole day meddling,
but it actually turned out
to be pretty peaceful.
Hey, wanna watch our show while we eat?
-Yeah.
-Huh?
-Um…
[both chuckle awkwardly]
[Anzu] I can't wait to see what happened
after the zombies caught them.
It's gonna be so good!
[suspenseful music]
-[screaming]
-[zombie snarling]
[Anzu screams]
That thing! It's back!
IT'S SUPER GROSS,
WE DISGUISED IT AS A CAKE
Kazuki, kill it! Kill it now!
Not again.
IT'S SUPER GROSS,
WE DISGUISED IT AS A CAKE
Hey, Junta, help me lift the couch.
-[whimpers]
-[Tsukasa] What?
[thuds]
Fine, I'll just get it myself!
-[grunts]
-[splats]
Man, I'm glad you're here.
Kazuki, I know moving in so quick
was kinda nuts,
but you've been a lifesaver for me.
[Junta] Unlike me,
I'm sorry I'm so useless.
Not true, Junta,
you caught that awful panty thief!
[Junta] I can't even protect you
from a bug.
[Anzu] Hey, no,
those things are the worst.
There. See?
[light music]
Maybe I'm the one who's being saved.
[sighs]
[Anzu] So far, the sleeping arrangements
have been kinda nice.
Might just work out after all.
[chuckling]
Oh no, I wouldn't get
so comfortable just yet.
I still have one more player for our game.
[birds chirping]
[snoring]
Wake up!
[gasps, screams]
Kazuki? Why are you in my room?
Well, I tried shouting from downstairs,
but you were out cold.
But my alarm…
Oh crap!
Just go! Go on without me!
-Yeah, I wasn't planning on waiting.
-[whimpers]
[door closes]
[Anzu] I've never overslept for school!
[pants, grunts]
How did this happen? I'm so screwed!
[breathing heavily]
Oh no, I'm gonna be late!
[Anzu] Wait. What did I just say?
That phrase…
It sounded so familiar.
I'm gonna be late!
[panting]
[both grunt]
[Anzu] This is way too similar
to one of those dating sim scenarios.
There's no chance
a third guy shows up, right?
I'm coming up on the corner.
You don't think…
Nah, there's no way.
I'm not even running with toast
in my mouth, so--
-[thuds]
-[screams]
[grunts]
[Anzu] Uh, it was just a car,
not another cute boy. I'm safe.
Wait! That car just hit me!
[groans]
[man] I'm terribly sorry, miss.
Are you hurt?
[moans]
[gentle music]
Uh…
I'm fine. Not even a scratch.
[Hijiri] She's the one who went running
out into the street right in front of us.
There's absolutely
no need for us to apologize to her.
[dreamy music]
You're the one
with the toast in your mouth?
[exhales deeply]
[munching]
A fanfare, please!
And a big congratulations!
Did you fall for my little trick?
I bet now you don't feel like
skipping the ending, right?
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪